// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "By which year does Accenture want to achieve a net zero carbon emission?",
    answer: "2025",
    options: [
      "2025",
      "2030",
      "2035",
      "2050"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What are the top three countries producing the most carbon dioxide?",
    answer: "USA, China, Russia",
    options: [
      "Russia, India, UK",
      "USA, China, Russia",
      "Australia, Ecuador, Philippines",
      "Italy, Brunei, Madagascar"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What source causes the most carbon emissions?",
    answer: "Transportation",
    options: [
      "Agriculture",
      "Electricity production",
      "Land use and forestry",
      "Transportation"
      
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What does carbon emissions mean?",
    answer: "Carbon dioxide emitted when fossil fuels are burned in vehicles and industrial processes",
    options: [
      "The carbon dioxide that is stored in your house",
      "Non-green house gas released into the atmosphere",
      "Carbon dioxide emitted when fossil fuels are burned in vehicles and industrial processes",
      "The pure carbon released into the atmosphere"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "When working out either in the morning or later in the evening which option below would have the smallest impact on the environment?",
    answer: "Exercising outdoors",
    options: [
      "Exercising outdoors",
      "Going to the gym",
      "Running on a treadmill at home",
      "Putting on a short exercise video"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "How many sustainability development goals (SDGs) are there?",
    answer: "17",
    options: [
      "10",
      "12",
      "17",
      "25"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which of the following is considered the least sustainable option when traveling?",
    answer: "Planes",
    options: [
      "Bikes",
      "Electric vehicles",
      "Public transportation",
      "Planes"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What fabric uses the least amount of water in its production?",
    answer: "Recycled PET Polyester",
    options: [
      "Cotton",
      "100% Organic cotton",
      "Polyester",
      "Recycled PET Polyester"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is the least carbon intensive way to go to the office?",
    answer: "Take the public bus",
    options: [
      "Drive a car",
      "Take the public bus",
      "Rent an electric scooter",
      "Rent a dock-less bike"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What is the main what is one of the main concerns of carbon emissions?",
    answer: "Increase in the temperature which leads to global warming",
    options: [
      "Decrease in the global temperature",
      "The atmosphere becomes cleaner",
      "The air is less polluted",
      "Increase in the temperature which leads to global warming"
    ]
  },
];